tikatoytradings.com 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy

We insist on the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy since we value the trust you place in us.

  * Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without prior notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.
  * By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our Website.
  * By mere use of the Website, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the Terms of Use.

#### Collection of Information

When you use our Website, we collect and store your personal information which is provided by you from time to time. We aim to provide you a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customize our Website to make your experience safer and easier. More importantly, while doing so we collect personal information from you that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose.

In general, you can browse the Website without revealing your identity or any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. Wherever possible, we indicate which fields are optional and which are required. You always have the option to not provide information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature on the Website. We may automatically track certain information about you based upon your behavior on our Website. We use this information to do internal research on our user's demographics, interests, and behavior to better understand, protect and serve our users. This information is compiled and analyses on an aggregated basis. This information may include the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Website or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Website or not), your computer browser information, and your IP address.

We use data collection devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of the Website to help analyses our web page flow, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again.

Additionally, you may encounter "cookies" or other similar devices on certain pages of the Website that are placed by third parties. We do not control the use of cookies by third parties.

We collect information about your buying behavior if you choose to buy on the Website.

In case you transact with us, we collect certain additional information, such as a billing address, credit / debit card number , expiration date,other payment details and tracking information from money orders and cheques.

In case you choose to post messages on our chat rooms, message boards or other message areas or leave feedback, we will collect that information you provide to us. We retain this information as necessary to resolve disputes, provide customer support and troubleshoot problems as permitted by law.

In case you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

We collect personally identifiable information (email address, name, phone number, credit card / debit card / other payment instrument details, etc.) when you set up a free account with us.

#### Use and Sharing of Information

At no time will we sell your personally-identifiable data without your permission unless set forth in this Privacy Policy. The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us or shared by us with our corporate affiliates, dealers, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our customers' needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services (of us or our business associates) in which you may be interested. We may also combine information you provide us with information about you that is available to us internally or from other sources in order to better serve you.

We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.

#### Cookies

"Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again.

From time to time, we may place "cookies" on your personal computer. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies certain features of the site may not function properly or at all as a result.

#### Links

Our website contains links to other sites. Such other sites may use information about your visit to this website. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to practices of such sites that we do not own or control or to people we do not employ. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the accuracy or the integrity of the content included on such other sites. We encourage you to read the individual privacy statements of such websites.

#### Security

We safeguard your privacy using known security standards and procedures and comply with applicable privacy laws. Our websites combine industry-approved physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to ensure that your information is well protected throughout it's life cycle in our infrastructure.

Sensitive data is hashed or encrypted when it is stored in our infrastructure. Sensitive data is decrypted, processed and immediately re-encrypted or discarded when no longer necessary. We host web services in audited data centers, with restricted access to the data processing servers. Controlled access, recorded and live-monitored video feeds, 24/7 staffed security and bio-metrics provided in such data centers ensure that we provide secure hosting.

#### Opt-Out Policy

All our users have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications.

Please email [info@tikatoytradings.com](mailto:privacy@infibeam.net)[](mailto:privacy@infibeam.net) if you no longer wish to receive any information from us.

#### Consent

By using the Website and/or by providing your information, you consent to the collection and use of the information you disclose on the Website in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to Your consent for sharing your information as per this privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time without notice. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically to make sure you are aware of any changes.

#### Questions

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail your questions to us at [info@tikatoytradings.com](mailto:privacy@infibeam.net)
